this is the first episode of FWD health
insurance my name is Chu a financial
wealth officer
first let's watch the set for health
promotional video 30 years ago getting
diagnosed with a major critical illness
was pretty much a death sentence but now
medical advancements have made it
possible for critical illness survivors
to enjoy longer and more productive
lives the catch living longer
potentially exposes us to more than one
major critical illness in our lifetime
and treatment will still cost you an arm
and a leg the second or third time if
you get coverage at all
introducing fwd's set for Health Plan
it's a one-of-a-kind plan that lets you
live a worry-free life through good
times and when things are not going so
well with set for help get covered for
42 major critical illnesses and claim
for up to three times for three
unrelated major critical illnesses up to
age 75. with 100 coverage each time to
help you fight and recover that's triple
protection for triple Peace of Mind
impressed we haven't even scratched the
surface yet if you get diagnosed with
your first major critical illness we'll
waive all future premiums and coverage
continues free of further charges so you
can focus on what matters most getting
well for 50 minor critical illnesses
you'll get ample coverage too one claim
up to 20 of the coverage amount to be
exact more than to help you with smaller
medical expenses which can still be a
financial burden but what if the
illnesses don't come knocking what if
life stays awesome until you're 75 and
you don't claim for a major critical
illness simple we'll give you 100 of
your premium back no questions asked
lastly what if the unthinkable happens
before you reach 75 and you pass away
FWD will look after your family by
giving them 100 of your plan's coverage
amount so they can financially be
worry-free purchase your set for health
plan today we've got you covered for a
lifetime of possibilities get ready to
live
foreign
brochure
set for health is a health protection
plan it focuses on Life protection
critical illness and return of premiums
claim up to three times for unrelated
major critical illnesses return of paid
premiums at age 75 if no major claims
are made waive payments upon first major
critical illnesses diagnosis or total
and permanent disability of the insured
a hundred percent coverage for 42 major
critical illnesses additional 20
coverage for 15 minor critical illnesses
and a hundred percent death benefit to
be given to your beneficiary
we are here for you no matter what what
is zero waste Health protection it means
getting a return from the premiums
you've paid whether you get sick stay
healthy or pass away it provides
protection for 42 major critical
illnesses wherein you can claim up to
three times for unrelated illnesses also
should you be fortunate to reach age 75
without ever needing to make a major
critical illness claim will give you all
your money back you can use this as an
additional retirement fund or as a
wellness fund to continue being healthy
we're rooting for you and want only for
you to have the best possible outcome in
life
claim up to three times for unrelated
major critical illnesses covers 42 major
critical illnesses and 15 minor critical
illnesses additional 20 cash benefit
subject to a maximum of 500 000 pesos if
diagnosed with one of the 15 covered
minor critical illnesses death benefit
for your loved ones if you pass away
before the age of 75 you can choose from
flexible payment terms 5 10 20 years if
you get diagnosed with a major critical
illness future premium payments will be
waived so you can focus on your recovery
a hundred percent per turn of premiums
paid if you don't make any major
critical illness claims up to the age
75. here we have a set for health sample
Journey the empowered side entrepreneur
at 35 years old Crystal has a full-time
job but also makes a good side income
selling Crafts online she does regular
yoga and goes for long walks to stay
healthy but being 35 years old she knows
she must invest in her health and future
so she's covered she wants a traditional
insurance policy and purchases set for
health for 32
215 pesos per year with a benefit amount
of 500 000 pesos and 10 years to pay
at 38 years old although Crystal eats
well and exercises she is diagnosed with
coronary artery disease which she seems
to have inherited from her father's side
with her first major critical illness
she receives 500 000 pesos while FWD
waives all her future premiums and keeps
her set for health coverage active
Crystal finds relief and focuses on
making a quick recovery
at 45 years old Crystal's business is
thriving but she suffered an aneurysm
and under one surgery to the aorta she
pays her medical expenses with another
500 000 pesos as her second major
critical illness benefit
at 50 years old five years on and
Crystal has made the move from a
full-time employee to a full-time
entrepreneur she spends plenty of time
traveling and tending to her business as
things often go Crystal experiences
another medical setback this time it's
bacterial meningitis she receives 500
000 pesos as her third major critical
illness benefit while recovering her
family tells her she is lucky to have
health care and she agrees she didn't
have to sacrifice her business or her
savings all she needed was some time off
to get better
at age 74. Crystal enjoys a long and
prosperous life in the company a family
and loved ones she's taken care
of her health at the age of 74 and
passes away
she leaves her sizable business to her
family from her set for health plan they
received 100 coverage amount of 500 000
pesos Crystal's investment in her health
paid off let her lived long and better
while leaving her family a final gift
another sample Journey the healthy
manager at 40 years old Carl is a health
buff and always finds time to work out
and go for runs on the weekend still he
wants to make sure he's covered in case
of emergency so he purchases set for
health with a benefit amount of 1
million pesos until age 75. for 132 300
pesos per year for five years at 50
years old Carl has enjoyed several
promotions over the last 10 years but
his work has taken a small toll on his
health he undergoes angioplasty which is
considered a minor condition and
receives 200 000 pesos from FWD
Carl is soon back on his feet and level
up his exercise routine with regular
walks and more weekend activities
at 75 years old Carl celebrates his 75th
birthday and looks bad grateful that
he's never had a major critical illness
all his exercise and Healthy Living paid
off his family gives him a giant
gluten-free cake his favorite but
perhaps the best part is he gets all his
paid premium back a healthy living
benefit of 661 thousand and 500 pesos
the policy ends the party continues and
Carl eats a little more cake to
celebrate
frequently asked questions so what
illnesses can or conditions are covered
so for major critical illnesses we have
five groups
first is for cancers second major organ
failure third heart and blood vessels
fourth neuromuscular related and fifth
is for others
below you can find here minor critical
illnesses for all ages and minor
critical illnesses for juvenile
conditions ages 0 to 17.
are my benefits guaranteed yes your
benefits are guaranteed as long as you
keep your policy active by paying your
premiums regularly
when can I claim my critical illness
benefit you may claim your benefit after
the initial 90-day no claim period that
starts from the effective date the last
reinstatement date or the date of
increase of benefit amount
you may also claim your benefit if the
diagnosis of the insured falls under
covered major or minor critical
illnesses
for multiple major critical illnesses
claims must belong to different
categories
in case of Group 1 or the cancer
category up to two major critical
illnesses Claims can be made as long as
the insured is declared cancer free for
five years prior to the diagnosis of the
second cancer
the insured must complete a 14-day
recovery period following the diagnosis
of the critical illness
are there instances when the critical
illness benefit will not be paid there
are a few situations where a benefit is
not given you cannot make a claim if the
critical illness is due to pre-existing
conditions drugs or alcohol abuse cancer
or Encephalitis in the presence of HIV
loss of independent existence due to
psychiatric causes attempted suicide or
intentional self-inflicted acts unlawful
acts of the insured are policy owner or
in case of War
when can the death benefit be payable
the death benefit is payable once the
policy starts as it is subject to the
90-day no claim period however the death
benefit may not be claimed if the death
of the insured is due to attempted
suicide or deliberate self-harm while
seeing within two years after the
coverage starts or is reinstated
in these cases we returned the total of
all paid premiums to the beneficiaries
I already have a medical condition or
family history can I still apply
we have several criteria in assessing
your application having a medical
condition or family history does not
mean that we will decline your
application right away we highly
encourage you to apply so you can
receive a proper assessment
I changed my mind can I get a refund
yes as long as it's within the 15-day
free look period during the period
uh during this period you can review the
policy Provisions
inclusions and exclusions up to 15 days
upon getting your contract if you do
decide to cancel the policy just let us
know and you will get a full refund
about FWD Insurance FWE Life Insurance
Corporation or FWD Insurance launched
its commercial operations September 2014
in just six years of business fwed
insurance now ranks third and fourth in
terms of paid up capital and new
business annual premium equivalent
respectively
swd group spans 10 markets in Asia
including as Hong Kong SAR and Macau SAR
Thailand Indonesia the Philippines
Singapore Vietnam Japan Malaysia and
Cambodia offering life medical insurance
General Insurance employee benefits
Sharia and family
tackle full products across a number of
its Market in the Philippines FWD has 18
business hubs located in key cities
Nationwide with its headquarters and
Bonifacio Global City and Taguig
established in Asia in 2013 with a
Trailblazer mentality FWD is the primary
Insurance business of Investment Group
Pacific Century group FWD is focused on
creating fresh customer experiences and
making Insurance Journeys simpler faster
and smoother with innovative
propositions and easy to understand
products supported by digital technology
through this customer-led approach FWD
aims to become a leading pan-Asian
influence insurer that changes the way
people feel about insurance for more
information you can visit our website
you can also contact me and check out
how you can grow your career with FWD
this is a set for health sales
illustration using my data be ready to
take on life's challenges we are pleased
to present this set for health sales
illustration to their proposed Insurance
name with a reference number
a complete detail and then the payment
frequency the amount of the sum assured
and the modal premium and the years to
be
on the second page we can see here set
for health is with you for the good
times and the bad fwed provides a
financial assistance so you can live
worry free and without hesitations these
are also the benefits that we've
mentioned from the product brochure
on the next page we see here a diagram
of how set for Health Works so upon
policy effective date death benefit is
already enforced if ever in case the
unthinkable happens we will give your
beneficiaries a lump sum payment of 100
of your sum assured in this case based
on our sales illustration it is 1
million pesos so if on the first year of
the policy you get your first major
critical illness example coronary heart
disease you will receive 100 of your sum
assured for each of your major critical
illnesses claims plus we will waive all
your future premiums upon diagnosis of
your first major critical illnesses so
in this case from the first diagnosis
itself of the major critical illness
your premiums are already ready waived
at the same time the policy is still in
force so if on the second year you get a
minor critical illness
here the example is an early stage
breast cancer then you can get a minor
critical illness benefit you will
receive an additional 20 of your sum
assured so 20 of 1 million
and then if ever on the next year on the
policy year three you get your second
major critical illness a benign brain
tumor you will receive another 100 of
your sum assured for this particular
major critical illness claim and then if
it so happens that you still get a third
major critical illness on the fifth year
which is a bacterial meningitis you will
still be able to receive 100 of your
summer assured for this particular major
critical illness claim and at the same
time
if ever
you really never got any major critical
illness benefit
so at the age of 75 you will get a
healthy life benefit you will receive
100 of total premiums so the beauty of
this particular product is that you can
claim three times for major critical
illness one out one time claim for a
minor critical illness benefit out of
the 15 minor critical illness listings
that we have and if ever you've never
used this particular product at the age
75 you're still healthy and very alive
then you will receive a hundred percent
of the total premiums at the same time
from the policy effective date up to the
age of 75 in case of any death
then you can receive a death benefit
which will give you a hundred percent of
your sum assured now each of your major
critical illness claims must belong to a
different major critical illness group
diagnosis of subsequent critical illness
should be at least one year from the
date of diagnosis of the preceding
critical illness you will be able to
claim for a second benefit under cancer
group for as long as you had been
declared cancer free at least five years
prior to the diagnosis of the second
cancer
no subsequent major critical illness
benefits will be paid if you have
already received a benefit due to
terminal illness or loss of independent
existence on the next page we see here
the sales illustration has been created
for you we see a table so the terms and
conditions applicable to your policy
will be presented in the actual policy
contract summary of benefits and
premiums we have here benefit
descriptions the period the percentage
of some assured or the total premiums
and the benefit amount so first we have
here the major critical illness benefits
for 49 years with a benefit percentage
of 100 of some assured per claim so in
this case it's a 1 million pesos per
claim up to three claims minor critical
illnesses for 49 years 20 some assured
or 500 000 pesos whichever is lower in
this particular case it's 200 and pesos
waiver of premium benefit for 20 years
because we are planning to be paying
this for 20 years so it's already
included
so if upon the first diagnosis of the
major critical illnesses
um waiver of premiums benefit will take
place
then we have here death benefit for 49
years a hundred percent of Summer short
which is 1 million pesos
and then we have a healthy life benefit
49 years a hundred percent of total
premiums that is 591 360 pesos so the
healthy life benefit is payable at the
end of the policy year upon reaching age
75 if no major critical illnesses
benefit has been paid
then it actually depends no so for us we
chose the monthly premium so that is
2464 pesos per month
and then we may review and adjust the
premium accordingly but with prior
approval from the insurance commission
FWD shall notify you before any such
adjustments
so we have here table of premiums and
cash values so since this is a
traditional Insurance it has a
guaranteed cash value we have see here
the policy here the age the annualized
premium guaranteed cash value
at the end of the policy year with and
without major critical illness claims
from the first policy year to the 49th
policy year
so we also have here uh listings of the
covered five major critical illnesses
groups on the next page we see here a
continuation of the 15 minor critical
illnesses covering Juvenile and adult
conditions so juvenile conditions for
ages 0 to 17 and adult conditions for 18
and above the benefit for a minor
critical illness is paid only once
either from an adult condition or from a
juvenile condition so here we see here
uh situations where benefits are not
payable
benefit payable shall be based on the
definitions and conditions of each
critical illness set out in the policy
contract covered critical illness is
payable if it occurs after 90 days from
the latter of the effective date or
reinstatement of your policy no benefit
will be payable if the major or minor
critical illness results primarily are
secondarily wholly or partly from any of
the following circumstances first
attempted suicide or intentional
self-inflicted act by the insured second
the willful participation of the insured
beneficiary or beneficiaries or the
owner and illegal and or unlawful acts
and or omissions third alcohol and drug
or drug abuse
fourth human immunodeficiency virus HIV
or
any HIV related illnesses including
acquired immune deficiency syndrome and
or any mutations
derivate derivations or variations
thereof accept occupational acquired
occupationally acquired HIV or Aids and
HIV or Aids due to blood transfusion as
stated to the eligible major critical
illness Provisions or war or any Act of
War whether declared or not civil or
military Insurrection and civil
commotion amounting to a popular
uprising
next a pre-existing condition as defined
in the policy contract we will only pay
the benefit if you have declared the
pre-existing condition in your
application form and we have included it
in our assessment of your application in
the event of insured that no benefits
will be paid in case of suicide within
the first two years while insured is
same
canceling this policy you can cancel
this policy by sending us a written
request within 15 days after it has been
delivered to you upon cancellation we
will return all your paid premiums for
this policy no interest will be paid on
the refunded amount if a claim is
payable for this policy before we
receive your written request for
cancellation we will not refund the
premiums
this is the last page where you can see
that there's an acknowledgment by the
owner so you just have the sign and
write the date accepted
so it says here I acknowledge that by
signing below I signify that I have
carefully read and understood the
disclosures and information contained in
the sales illustration and that my
financial wealth planner has fully
explained to my complete satisfaction
the principal features and benefits of
this plan this sales illustration is
valid for three months from the date it
was prepared and any alteration shall
invalidate the sales illustration
set for health was made for people and
with purpose so the reason why we made
set for health is to make sure that
everyone can be able to get a secured
quality of life as we all know health is
wealth and health is the only thing that
we truly possess
set for health has an online shop and
this is the beauty of having to work
with FWD because our clients can already
experience online shopping for insurance
visit our online shop and get your set
for health plan this is the online shop
for FWD insurance so you can just copy
the link or type in the link and then
you see here set for health digital
digital critical illness Insurance you
just click the get a cool and then you
can follow on and input your data and it
would also give you a Sample Sales
illustration with the amount of premiums
that we would need to pay and all the
benefits and exclusions will also be
provided this has been through a
financial wealth officer and a financial
planner you can call me at Viber or via
Facebook page through Chuan Chu and get
ready to live with set for health